One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Big Showdown on the Judicial Island!
المعركة الفاصلة !في الجزيرة القضائية
A-Another report from the main gate!
تـ-تقرير آخر من البوابة الرئيسة
What is it this time?!
ما الأمر هذه المرة؟
A suspicious group in a monster-drawn wagon just flew over the front fence!
مجموعة مشبوهة على عربة وحوش اجتازت السياج الحديدي توًّا
Please send reinforcements!
أرسلوا الدعم من فضلكم
Please send–
...أرسلوا
What happened?!
ماذا حدث؟
Gatekeeper!
يا حارس البوابة
Come in!
استجب
What is going on?!
ماذا يجري؟
What's the matter, Nico Robin?
ما الخطب يا نيكو روبين؟
Don't stop.
لا تتوقفي
Are you guys ready?
هل أنتم مستعدون؟
How are your wounds?
ماذا عن جراحك؟
I'll be okay, because...
...أنا بخير وهذا لأنني
I'm Sogeking!
سوغيكينغ
In four minutes, the sea train Rocketman will charge in!
سيقتحم القطار البحري روكيت مان المكان بعد أربع دقائق
Main Gate
البوابة الرئيسة
Island Gate
بوابة الجزيرة
Excuse me, but... please let me through.
المعذرة، ولكن اسمحوا لي بالعبور
Even if you ask nicely...
...حتّى وإن طلبت بلطف
"no" means...
فلا تعني لا
Then...
...إذًا
brace yourselves!
استعد
Cocky pirate!
تبًّا لك أيها القرصان
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط
Ally Robot!
الآلي الحليف
Hey! That's dirty!
هذا قذر
We can't hit him now!
لا نستطيع مهاجمته هكذا
What a childish trick!
هذه خدعة واضحة، لا تترددوا
Ally Robot...
لكمة الآلي الحليف
Sorry!
أعتذر
Ally Robot Kick!
ركلة الرفيق الآلي
I'm so sorry, sir!
أعتذر يا سينباي
That's enough!
يكفي، ظهرك مكشوف
You bastard!
!وغد
Bring him down!
تخلّصوا منه، إنه مجرد رجل واحد غير مسلّح
How in the world is he so agile?!
ما هذه الرشاقة؟
I'm in a hurry.
أنا في عجلة من أمري
More people are coming later!
سيأتي مزيد من الناس لاحقًا... إلى اللقاء
He got through! Hurry! Get inside!
دخل، أسرعوا إلى الداخل
He's on the main island!
دخل حقًّا
Chief, this is the island gate reporting!
هذه بوابة الجزيرة، تقرير إلى الرئيس
S-Straw Hat Luffy has set foot on the main island!
د-دخل قبعة القش لوفي إلى الجزيرة الرئيسة
What?! You let him onto the main island?!
ماذا؟ سمحتم له بدخول الجزيرة الرئيسة؟
What the hell is going on?!
ماذا يجري؟
What are Oimo and Kashi doing?!
ماذا حدث لأويمو وكاشي؟
Did he take them out too?!
أهُزما أيضًا؟
No, sir! It's the middle of the night right now, so...
لا، بما أننا في منتصف الليل
they're probably asleep.
فإنهما نائمان على الأرجح
This is no time to be sleeping!
أتراه وقت النوم؟ أيقظوهما
Wake all the guards on the main island too!
وأيقظوا جميع حرس الجزيرة الرئيسة أيضًا
R-Roger!
حـ-حاضر
It's just an intruder.
إنه مجرد دخيل
That's no reason to make such a fuss, right, Chief?
لا داعي لكلّ هذه الضجة يا رئيس
You've got us.
فنحن هنا
Don't be ridiculous!
كفاك سخافة، هذه الجزيرة القضائية
Any idiot should know what it means to invade this place!
أيُّ أحمقٍ يُفترض أن يدرك ما يعنيه اقتحام هذا المكان
And yet, he broke through to the main island just to take back a single crew member!
ومع ذلك، دخل حتى الجزيرة الرئيسة لاستعادة رفيق واحد
It's an embarrassment! Who does he think we are?!
هذا مخزٍ، كيف يجرؤون الاستخفاف بنا؟
Damn those Straw Hats and their accomplices!
تبًّا لطاقم قبعة القش ولأتباعهم
Gatekeeper!
يا حارس البوابة، اشرح لي ما يجري عند البوابة الرئيسة
Hey, gatekeeper!
يا حارس البوابة
How many enemies are there?
كم عدد الأعداء؟
Where are they?
ما موقعهم الحالي؟
Come in, main gate!
استجيبوا يا من عند البوابة الرئيسة
Hey, what's the matter?!
ما خطبكم؟
Rope Action...
قتال الحبال
Figure-of-Eight Knot!
عقدة شكل رقم ثمانية
Bazooka Bat!
مضرب البازوكا
Shouldn't waste our ammo just yet!
لا أريد تضييع الطلقات بعد
Get in through the side doors! Open the gate!
ادخلوا من البوابات الجانبيّة وافتحوا البوابة
Don't let them open it!
لا تسمحوا لهم بفتحها
– Move it or lose it!
لا تعق طريقنا
Mozu! Take the left side!
امضي يسارًا يا موزو
I'm on it!
مفهوم
Like I'd let you!
لن أسمح لك
Whoa! Hair just popped out of my nose!
خرجت شعرة من أنفي
You should pay attention!
لا ينبغي أن يتشتت انتباهك
Get going!
أسرعي
Thanks a bunch!
شكرًا
Keel Breaker!
مُحطّم العارضة
Are the gates unlocked yet?! Mozu?! Kiwi?!
ألم تنتهيا بعد يا موزو وكيوي؟
Ship demolition is the Franky Family's job. So picking locks is...
...هدم السفن هي وظيفة عائلة فرانكي، فإنَّ فتح مفتاحًا كهذا
Unlocked on this side!
فتح من جانبي
This side too!
ومن جانبي أيضًا
Okay then! Open the gate, Mighty Destroyers!
حسنٌ، افتحوا البوابة أيها المدمرون الخارقون
Don't let them open it! Defend it at all costs!
لا تسمحوا لهم بفتحها، احموها بأيّ ثمن
Move! You're in our way!
ابتعدوا، إنّكم تعيقون طريقنا
Hurry through!
اندفعوا
We broke through the first gate!
اخترقنا البوابة الأولى
Whoa! What the hell is with this gaping hole?!
ما هذه الحفرة؟
There's no time for sightseeing!
لا وقت لدينا، تجاهلوها وتقدموا
Stay the course and get to the island gate!
استمروا بالتقدم واركضوا نحو بوابة الجزيرة
It's a waterfall!
إنه شلّال
– We did it!
نجحنا
Hey, guys! Over here!
من هنا يا جماعة
Gimme a hand with this!
ساعدوني بسرعة
Kashi! Oimo! Wake up this instant!
!كاشي-سان! أويمو-سان! استيقظا بسرعة
Th-The main gate has been forced open by intruders!
فتح الدخلاء البوابة
He said the main gate was forced open, Oimo.
قال أنهم فتحوا البوابة يا أويمو
Yeah.
أجل، هذا سيّئ يا كاشي
I don't wanna get up...
أكره الاستيقاظ مجبرًا
...but it's our job. Let's go do this.
ولكن هذا عملنا، لنذهب
– What?!
ماذا؟
Oimo Gatekeeper of Enies Lobby's Island Gate
أويمو حارس لبوابة إنيس لوبي الرئيسة
Kashi Gatekeeper of Enies Lobby's Island Gate
كاشي
I didn't get enough sleep.
لم أحظَ كفايتي من النوم بعد
I'll get rid of them quick and go back to bed.
سأتخلّص منهم بسرعة وأعود للنوم
Oimo too.
أنا أيضًا
G-G-Giants!
عـ-عـ-عملاقان
Dunno why you guys came all the way here,
لا أدري لماذا أتيتم كلّ الطريق إلى هنا
but I suggest you turn tail before we crush you.
ولكن من الأفضل أن ترجعوا قبل أن نحطمكم
Right, Oimo?
صحيح يا أويمو؟
Yeah, Kashi. Oimo agrees.
نعم يا كاشي، أوافقك
We'll crush you flat, bones and all!
سنسحق حتّى عظامكم
Giant gatekeepers?!
حراس بوابة عمالقة؟ هذا غير عادل
They're huge! They make our Mighty Destroyers look tiny.
إنهما عملاقان، حتّى محطمونا الخارقون يبدون صغارًا بالنسبة لهم
Now, turn back!
فلتعودوا
I won't let you through this gate!
لن أسمح لكم بعبور هذه البوابة
Neither will Oimo!
وأنا أيضًا
Here they come!
سيأتيان
No matter our foe, stand tall, Franky Family!
مهما كان خصمنا، فلا تتوانوا يا عائلة فرانكي
This is for Bro!
هذا من أجل أخينا
– Yeah!
أجل
Hey, you get it, right?
تفهمون معنى هذا، صحيح؟
Yeah.
نعم
All right!
حسنًا
If not us, then who could possibly face 'em?!
إن لم نهجم، فمن سيفعل؟
Dismantling ships has made us powerful enough to match these giants any day!
القوى الخارقة التي اكتسبناها بعملنا في هدم السفن تساوي قوّة العمالقة
Destroyers!
المدمرون
O-Our Mighty Destroyers were...!
ا-المدمرون الخارقون
It happened so fast!
...بلحظة واحدة
We were born warriors!
وُلدنا محاربين
The blood in our veins is different from that of overgrown humans.
الدماء الجارية في عروقنا مختلفة عنكم أيها البشر الصغار الذي صدف أنّكم أكبر قليلًا من الآخرين
I'm not gonna let even a single person pass!
لن أسمح بعبور أحد
Neither will Oimo!
أنا أيضًا
D-D-Don't get cold feet!
لـ-لـ-لا ترتعبوا، لا تستسلموا
That's right! Big Bro Franky is on the other side of that gate!
صحيح، أخونا فرانكي في الجانب الآخر من تلك البوابة
Show them a fight worthy of Bro's name, Franky Family!
!لنقاتلهم قتالًا يستحق حمل اسم أخينا يا عائلة فرانكي
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
يا قبعة القش لوفي
How many friends did you bring?
كم عدد رفاقك الذين جلبتهم؟
There are 10,000 soldiers on Enies Lobby!
يوجد عشرة آلاف جندي في إنيس لوبي
Yeah, I'm by myself.
أجل، أنا وحدي
And you're in my way!
أفسحوا الطريق
Show them a fight worthy of Bro's name, Franky Family!
!لنقاتلهم قتالًا يستحق حمل اسم أخينا يا عائلة فرانكي
Don't give up!
لا تتوانوا، أفسحوا الطريق لروكيت مان
Break open the gate!
افتحوا البوابات
We're not gonna let even an ant pass through this gate!
لن نسمح حتّى لنملة بعبور هذه البوابة
Destroyers!
المدمرون
Everyone!
الجميع
Dammit! You've already beaten some of our strongest men?!
سحقًا، كيف تجرؤون على الإطاحة بأقوى صفوفنا؟
Go!
انطلق
What the...?!
ما هذا؟
Zambai!
زامباي
Kiwi! Mozu!
كيوي، موزو
Galley-La!
غاليلا
Sorry we're late!
نعتذر من تأخرنا
Switching Sodom and Gomorrah to land mode took longer than expected!
استغرق منّا تحويل سودوم وغومورا إلى النمط الأرضي وقتًا أكثر مما توقعنا
Zambai! The Destroyers...!
...يا زامباي، إنّ المدمرين
I know.
أعلم
But we can't stop to patch them up just yet.
لا وقت لدينا لمعالجتهم
In order to get to where Bro is, we have to open this gate at any cost!
علينا فتح البوابة مهما كان الثمن لغاية إنقاد أخينا فرانكي
Let's go!
لننطلق
Yeah!
أجل
Let's throw him off balance, Mozu!
لنفقده توازنه يا موزو
Roger, Kiwi!
مفهوم يا كيوي
– Hull Dismantler Slash!
قطع تفكيك هيكل السفينة
Rope Action...
قتال الحبال
Timber Hitch Tug!
سحب عقدة الأخشاب
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم
Kashi!
كاشي
Tilestone!
تايلستون
Yeah!
أجل
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم
Trunnel Lock!
قفل الوتد الخشبي
A job well done!
اكتمل العمل
You rats!
أيها الأوغاد
I'm gonna crush you!
سأحطّمكم
Kashi!
!كاشي
All right!
مرحى
How dare you...!
أيها الأوغاد
Just one more to go, gang!
لنطح بالآخر يا رجال
– Yeah!
أجل
So, what's the current situation?
كيف الأوضاع الحالية؟
Sir, Kashi and Oimo are dealing with them right now, in front of the island gate.
حاضر، يتعامل معهم كاشي وأويمو حاليًا أمام بوابة الجزيرة
We don't foresee any issues.
فلا أتوقع أي مشكلات
I see.
فهمت، أقبضتم على قبعة القش الذي اقتحم الجزيرة الرئيسة إذًا؟
Well... uh...
...حسنٌ
this is just an estimate, but there are about 400...
...هذا مجرد تقدير، لكنها تقريبًا أربعمئة
Four hundred?
أربعمئة؟
Our casualties, sir!
خسائرنا
Huh?! Our casualties?!
ماذا؟ خسائرنا؟
Are you saying that 400 guards are down?!
أتعني أن أربعمئة حارس هُزم؟
You can probably add a hundred more...
...أراهم زادوا مئة أخرى
Uh, apologies. I need to revise that estimate.
اعذرني، سأصحّح العدد
One would hope! Our guards aren't exactly trash.
طبعًا، حراسنا ليسوا قمامة
There's no way it's that many!
هزيمة كل ذلك القدر مُحالة
If there are casualties, report them accurately!
إن كان هنالك خسائر فأبلِغ عددهم بدقة
Um... Very well. Here is the report.
حسنًا إذًا، تفضّل التقرير
As of now, the casualty count is five–
...خسائرنا الحالية هنا خمس
Five guards?!
خمسة؟ مجرد خمسة حراس إذًا؟
Come on! You can't even make a proper report!
يا رجل، أليس بوسعك حتى إبلاغ تقرير جيد؟
Five... hundred... gu...
...خمس... مئة... حـ
Rather than fighting, Straw Hat Luffy is just running around the island.
يبدو أنّ قبعة القش لوفي لا يقاتل بل يهرب في أرجاء الجزيرة فحسب
Well, that's just natural.
لكن هذا طبيعي، فلا أحمق إلى درجة قتاله كل ذلك القدر من الحراس
It's just a matter of time before he's captured.
القبض عليه مسألة وقت
Welcome back, sirs and madam.
أهلًا بعودتكم
Chief, Mr. Lucci's party has arrived.
يا رئيس، فرقة لوتشي وصلت
They're back?
عادوا إذًا؟
Let them in!
أدخِلْهم
Hey, Sogeking...
أنت يا سوغيكينغ
Hey!
أنت
Hey, that hurt!
هذا مؤلم
How do I use this cold air baton?
...بخصوص استخدام عصا الطقش هذه للهواء البارد
Huh? Let me see...
...دعيني أرى
I wouldn't know!
وما أدراني؟
Now, guys! It's time!
إنه الوقت يا جماعة
Let's go, shall we?
هلّا ذهبنا
They should've opened those two gates by now.
أفترض أنهم فتحوا بوابتين الآن
Charge ahead! Charge ahead!
اقتحموا المكان، اقتحموا المكان
Samurai man! Take care of the iron fence!
أيها الساموراي، اعتنِ بأمر السياج الحديدي
Leave it to me.
اتركي الأمر لي